# RICHARD ALMEIDA

DATA ANALYST

786.222.6591

✓ RichardAlmeida@hotmail.com

Hollywood, FL.

English & Spanish

#### SKILLS

- Excel . PowerPoint . Word
- SQL
- Power BI . Tableau
- Python & R (novice)
- Data Visualization
- Analytical Skill (Facebook Ad Metrics)
- HTML . CSS . JAVA(novice)
- Adobe Suite Tools
- Computer Literacy
- Strong Communication

# **EDUCATION**

GOOGLE DATA ANALYTICS
PROFFESIONAL CERTIFICATE
2022

KEISER UNIVERSITY 2007-2009

BROWARD COLLEGE 2004 - 2007

## PROFILE

Highly motivated, team-oriented, and committed individual with several years of IT & web content creation. looking for a full-time position in Data Analytics in which I can grow my Analytical and Data visualization skills to work. serve, produce quality work, and excel.

PORTFOLIO: CLASHOFALLSTYLES.GITHUB.IO

### EXPERIENCE

#### WEB CONTENT MANAGER

Shopify . Digital marketer . Sales

2016 - Present

- Complete projects from conception to development including logo design, web design, branding, & social media management.
- Integrate integral SEO technique & Meta keywords
- Utilize multiple software applications including; Photoshop,
   Illustrator, and Davinci resolve media editor.
- Managed Facebook Ads marketing strategies & analyzing Facebook
   Ads sales data metrics.

#### LAWERS OFFICE OF STEPHAN PLANT

Office Specialist . Head of IT

2010 - 2014

- Provide Office technical support for Desktops PC, Printers, Networking, Servers, & Software updates/drivers
- Website design including logo design, web design, branding, & social media management.
- Integrate integral SEO technique & Meta keywords
- Utilize multiple software applications including; Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, & Dreamweaver.